# **VAIBHAV DESHMUKH**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vaibhavpd

• +918983476205 • vaibhavpradipdeshmukh@gmail.com

Passionate about Technology, Blogging and Digital Marketing, have the ability to possess new ideas, have intermediate level experience in Creative Content Writing, Social Media Management, Wordpress, Canva and beginner level experience in SEO Management, Wordpress, Adword, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects. Have dedication and determination towards work. I am able to adapt myself with the requirements of the organization.

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Digital Marketing Executive at Excelsior Research Pvt.Ltd.,
January 2019- Present

- Defined Digital Marketing Strategy for Brand Awareness.
- SEO management for website.
- Improved Social Media presence of company using engaging content.
- Creation of Graphical and Video content.

Digital Marketing Executive at VR 360 Degree Solutions India Pvt.Ltd.,
June 2018- November 2018

- Created content for blog & Website.
- Designed Wordpress websites for clients.
- Social Media Marketing For products.

Digital Marketing Intern at VR 360 Degree Solutions India Pvt.Ltd., March 2018- June 2018

- Created unique & engaging content for social media platforms
- Managed Social Media Accounts

### **EDUCATION**

Course	Institution	Examination Authority	Year of Passing	Marks
Engineering	SKN Sinhgad Institute Of Technology And Science	Savitribai Phule Pune University	2017	Appear
Diploma	SSP Institute Of Technology,Chopda Dist. Jalgaon	MSBTE	2013	60.00%
S.S.C	Vivekanand Vidyalaya, Chopda. Dist. Jalgaon	Maharashtra State Board	2009	79.84%

## **SKILLS**

- > Graphics and Video creation using Adobe and other tools (Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects, Canva)
- > Content writing & marketing using Wordpress CMS.
- Social Media Marketing on Facebook, LinkedIn, Etc.
- ➤ Keyword Research using Adword Keyword Research Tool, SEMRUSH, Etc.
- Email marketing using Mailchimp.
- > Team Player.
- Quick Learner.

## **PERSONAL DETAILS**

- Name:- Vaibhav Pradip Deshmukh.
- > Date Of Birth :- 13-08-1993.
- Address:- 201, Ballaleshwar Park, Rahatani, Pune 411017.
- Languages Known:- Marathi, Hindi, English.